nullednerd.com 2017-07-23

# Privacy Policy - NulledNerd.com

## **Privacy Policy**

we know that your number one concern is that we meet the security and privacy standards you expect. You should be aware of the following safety and privacy issues when you browse our website.

 **What information is collected by NulledNerd.Com?**

Standard use of the Site

In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information. The only information we gather during a general navigation on the Site is the information intended for the server logs: IP (Internet Protocol) address, domain name, browser type, operating system and information such as the site from which you are connected, pages visited, and the dates and times of those visits.

Collect of Personal Information

If you subscribe to a newsletter, log on, request information, send any comments or if you join a discussion group or electronic mailing list, you will need to provide some personal information: name and e-mail address, for example. Such information is collected only with your permission and is stored in different databases and mailing lists belonging to NulledNerd.

The registration of personal information leads to the submission of a cookie* on certain parts of NulledNerd. By setting this cookie, NulledNerd will remember your personal details at the next visit so you do not have to re-enter the same information. This helps us to improve the quality of services that we offer.

Participation in electronic discussion groups means that other participants in the group that you have chosen (including those who are not Site Administrators) will be aware of any personal information that you choose to disclose. In some open discussion groups, the information is public.

 **What does NulledNerd do with the information it collects?**

Standard use of the Site

The information collected during the navigation in the “ **NulledNerd.com** ” area is used to analyze trends and the use of the site in order to improve its usefulness. No personal information is attached there.

Personal Information

NulledNerd may use such information to:

* Contact you – either in response to a request or a suggestion, or to send you news, documents, publications, and so on;

* Confirm your entries on the site;

* “Remember” your online profile and preferences;

* Statistical analysis performing.

 **What will happen if I do not want to provide personal information?**

Providing personal information on the Site is optional. If you do not want to deliver information of this kind, you can always surf the Site, but you will not be able to access the entire Service and its Information.

Removal or modification of information

You can delete or modify your personal information at any time by returning to the page where you registered them or by contacting the coordinator of the page. If the page in question does not provide any information on this subject, you can contact Us for more information.

If you are not the issuer of personal information that concerns you and wants to have it removed, you can contact Us

Security

The personal data entrusted to the Site will not be sold or transferred to any third party. Any information provided to NulledNerd by users of the Site is preserved with the utmost care and maximum safety. It will be used only in the manner described in this privacy policy, or according to the special rules of visited sites or in a manner to which you have explicitly consented. NulledNerd uses techniques and a variety of measures to ensure the safety of information stored in its systems and protects them from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

All our volunteers who have access to personal information or are associated with the processing of these data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of every user of the Site, which covers the personal information.

The Site provides links to sites outside the “nulledNerd.com” area and could not be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content located on them.

Modifications

Any modification of these terms can be made at any time without prior publication or announcement.

Contact

For any questions or inquiries about our privacy policy, you can[ contact us](http://www.nullednerd.com/contact-us/)

 **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, the subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
